

## **CV** Website

# **CONTACTS**



+38 098-46-25-714

+38 050-471-60-06



martmarchmartmarch@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ oleksii-hiriavenko/



https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/

# **PRO.SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap

JavaScript

NodeJs (basics)

React, Redux (Thunk, Toolkit), MUI, etc

Git, GitLab, GitHub

Gulp, Webpack, Vite

Vercel, Netlify, Heroku, Swagger

Figma, Trello

# **English**

B1 - Intermediate (certificate)

## **EDUCATION**

10.2022 - 09.2023

**FRONTEND** 

**DAN.IT Education (certificate)** 

2022 - present

#### **SELF-EDUCATION**

EPAM: frontend self paced online program

RS-School: Frontend, Nodejs basics

Udemy: React, Redux

CodeWars ශු

2002 - 2007

### PROCESSING EQUIPMENT ENGINEER

Specialist (diploma)

**Donetsk National University of Economics and Trade** 

# CERTIFICATES

# **Oleksiy Hiryavenko**

# Frontend Developer

## **SUMMARY**

A switcher with many years of experience in marketing and purchasing management, passionate about front-end and programming in general. Participant of the IT generation project with the support of the Ministry of Digital Policy of Ukraine. I have the necessary technology stack to develop modern applications and user interfaces

# **PROJECTS**





#### • Social Network. React App with server & database

technologies React - ReduxToolkit - Formic - RouterDom - Material UI -

WebSocket - MongoDB - Express - Trello

https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/social-network/tree/develop source https://fs-social-network.netlify.app/ website for logIn check Link

#### • Privilege Handmade. React app. Online Store.

React - Redux - Formic - RouterDom ContextApi - Tests technologies source https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/onlineStore-HandMade

website https://privilege-handmade.netlify.app/

#### Medical Portal

technologies JS classes, Fetch API, Bootstrap, Responsive design, Gulp

source https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/medical-portal

website https://medical-portal.netlify.app/ for logIn check Link

#### Brooklyn Library

JavaScript, CSS. (auth, slider, tabs, user profile, store, etc) technologies

source Github

Library project link website

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

#### DAN.IT

10.2022 - 09.2023

Four modules completed during the year. Successfully completed five projects (all scores above 90%) using the stack of technologies mentioned above. Gained experience of working in a team (2, 3, 9 people). In one of the projects, I served as a team lead.

- HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- Advanced: HTML, CSS, SCSS. Responsive design.
- Advanced JavaScript, testing, Bootstrap
- React & Redux(thunk, toolkit), routing, Formik, MUI, testing,
- Introduction to Node.js, Express & Mongo DB

### PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

PURCHASING MANAGER

VHH Group 2019 - present

Provision of production with the necessary equipment, components, tools, materials

CATEGORY PURCHASING MANAGER

LLC "Effect" 2013 - 2019

Purchase of goods, increased sales, and improved turnover of inventory.

SALES AND MARKETING SPECIALIST

Amstor Retail Group 2006 - 2013

Product promotion and sales increase